(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-13T23:54:43.377395",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
超超超！重大告知アリ！完全生3D Acoustic Live in Autumn
Super, super, super! Major announcement included! Fully live 3D Acoustic Live in Autumn
跳ねた 跳ねた 僕は跳ねた
I hopped, I hopped, I hopped,
小学生みたいに
just like an elementary school kid.
雨上がりの 夜に跳ねた
I hopped in the night after the rain,
水たまりみたいに
just like a puddle.
見ていた フリしていた
Pretending to watch...
明日をすっ飛ばし
...skipping over tomorrow...
夜に逃げただけ
...we only fled into the night.
明日をすっ飛ばし
Skipping over tomorrow...
跳ねた 跳ねた 君も跳ねた
You hopped, you hopped, you hopped too,
小学生みたいに
just like an elementary school kid.
三つ目の眼も 開けて跳ねた
Opening even my third eye, I hopped,
アメンボみたいに
just like a pond skater.
忘れた フリして
Pretending to forget...
それはつまり
...which is to say,
夜に逃げただけ
we only fled into the night.
どこへ行こう どこへ行こう
Where shall we go? Where shall we go?
ここにいようとして
Trying to stay right here,
逃げるよ 逃げるよ
we'll run away, we'll run away,
あと少しだけ
just a little longer.
消えた 消えた 君が消えた
You faded, you faded, you faded away,
蜃気楼みたいに にわか雨の
like a mirage, in a sudden shower...
音も消えた
The sound also faded away,
さよなら言うように
as if saying goodbye...
(きこえたふりして)
(Pretending to hear...)
君の言う通り
Just as you said,
(夜に逃げただけ)
(we only escaped into the night.)
どこへ行こう
Where shall we go?
ここに居ようとしてる？
Are we trying to stay here?
逃げても
Even if we run,
even if we run,
音はもうしなくて
there's no sound anymore.
雨になって 何分か後に行く
It turns into rain, and I'll go a few minutes later.
今泣いて 何分か後に行く
Crying now, I'll go a few minutes later.
今泣いて 何分か後の自分
Crying now, my future self a few minutes from now.
今泣いて 何分か後に行く
Crying now, I'll go a few minutes later.
今泣いて 何分か後に言う
Crying now, I'll say it a few minutes later.
今泣いて 何年か後の自分
Crying now, my future self years from now.
行けるよ
We can go,
we can go.
遠くへ行こうとしてる
Trying to go far away...
イメージしよう
Let's imagine,
let's imagine...
自分が思うほうへ
Toward the direction we think of.
雨になって 何分か後に行く
It turns into rain, and I'll go a few minutes later.
今泣いて 何分か後に行く
Crying now, I'll go a few minutes later.
今泣いて 何分か後の自分
Crying now, my future self a few minutes from now.
今泣いて 何分か後に行く
Crying now, I'll go a few minutes later.
今泣いて 何年か後の自分
Crying now, my future self years from now.
笑っていたいだろう
You'd want to be laughing, right?
はい！ということで！
Yes! And with that!
ホロアコースティックライブ始まりました！
The holoAcousticLive has officially begun!
楽しいね！
This is so fun!
はい、1曲目はしっとり始まったかと思いきや、元気にいく『夜の踊り子』で
Yes, we thought we'd start off gently, but instead we kicked off energetically with "Yoru no Odoriko"!
始めさせていただきました！
We got started with that!
最高でした！最高！
That was amazing! The best!
ちょっと気持ちよくなって...
I got a bit carried away...
最後のほう、ハモり、間違えちゃった。
and messed up the harmony at the very end!
ハモりに行きそびれましたけどね、失礼いたしました。
I totally missed my cue to harmonize, my apologies!
ということで、本日一緒に歌ってくださるメンバーがあと2人いるので、全員呼びたいと思います！どうぞー！
Anyway! We have two more members singing with us today, so let's call everyone out! Come on in!
どうぞー！イェーイ！おーい！盛り上がりすぎじゃない？
Welcome! Yay! Whoa, aren't you guys a little too excited?
カメラワークもこだわってましたね。
The camerawork was really detailed too.
MVっぽい感じでやってくださった人（スタッフさん）がすごいこだわってやっていただきました。
Yes, the staff made it feel like a real music video with so much care.
ちーす、ちーす、ちーす！
Cheers, cheers, cheers!
それではまずは、今日一緒に歌っていただく皆さん、自己紹介をお願いしたいと思います！まずはAZKiちゃんから！
First off, I'd like everyone who is singing with us today to introduce themselves! Starting with AZKi-chan!
はーい！こんこんこんこん、こあずき！右手にマイク、左手に地図、
Hello! Kon kon kon kon, Ko-AZKi! Mic in my right hand, map in my left,
あなたのハートをゼロゲッサー！AZKiでーす！よろしくお願いします！
geoguessing your heart! I'm AZKi! Nice to meet you!
第2回に引き続き、呼んでいただきありがとうございます。
Thank you so much for inviting me back following the second acoustic live.
「第2回いつあるんですか？」って、AZKiちゃんがちょいちょい聞いてくれた。
AZKi-chan kept asking me, "When is the second one happening?"
でもなんかもう一回やろうっていう、勇気に本当に繋がったんで、感謝しております。ありがとうございます。
But that actually gave me the courage to do it again, so I'm truly grateful. Thank you so much!
よろしくお願いします。
Nice to be here.
そして、トワ様ー！
And next, Towa-sama!
はーい、こんやっぴー！ホロライブの、ホロライブ4期生...
Hello, kon-yappi! Hololive's... Hololive 4th generation...
ここ、一番大事なところ... / ややこしいやつ来た。
That was the most important part... / A complicated one has arrived!
ホロライブの常闇トワ様です！はい、よろしくお願いいたします！
Hololive's Tokoyami Towa-sama! Yes, nice to meet you!
トワ様ー！
Towa-sama!
嬉しい。マブと思ってますので、勝手に。
I'm so happy. I unilaterally think of us as best buds.
温度感違いますけど大丈夫ですか？ / どうかな？
The level of enthusiasm is a bit different, but is that okay? / Is it, though?
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you so much!
そして！なんと、今日のためにインドネシアから日本に来てくれた…
And! Surprisingly, having come to Japan from Indonesia just for today...
コボ！
Kobo!
はい！Kobo Kanaeru at your service! Let me be your sun to shine your day!
Hi! Kobo Kanaeru at your service! Let me be your sun to shine your day!
Kobo Kanaeru, rain shaman desu from Hololive, HoloID! よろしくお願いします！
Kobo Kanaeru, rain shaman desu from Hololive, HoloID! Please treat me well!
HoloID!
Yes! Terima kasih!
Yes! Thank you!
Sama-sama!
You're welcome!
「どういたしまして」って意味だよね。
That means "you're welcome," right?
本当に嬉しい！
I'm really so happy!
もう1曲目から、ね、togetherしてもらいまして。
Since the very first song, we got to sing together!
このあともよろしくお願いします！ノリノリで可愛い！
Please look forward to the rest! She's so energetic and cute!
始まる前、「緊張する！」って言ってて。
Before we started, she was like, "I'm so nervous!"
いやいやいや！めちゃめちゃかっこよかったよ！
No way! You were so cool!
ね、堂々と。
Yes, so confident.
めっちゃ自信ある。
I'm super confident.
Okay! かっこいいHoloID！ Very good!
Okay! Cool HoloID! Very good!
では、続きまして。
Now, moving on.
歌声が大好きな、ニコたん！
Someone whose singing voice I love... Niko-tan!
ニコたんが来た！
Niko-tan is here!
Hololive DEV_IS FlowGlow...
うわー！噛んだー！
Oh no, she stumbled!
はい！ニコたん！
All right! Niko-tan!
FlowGlowの割れたとこからニコです！
I'm Niko from the crack of FlowGlow!
イェーイ！
Yay!
何もなかったかのように。最近自己紹介が変わった？ちょっと緊張してますね。
Act like nothing happened! Did your intro change recently? I guess you're nervous.
もう1曲歌ったしね。ちょっと休んでね。
You already sang one song. Take a little break.
歌うと、脳が切り替わっちゃって。
When I sing, my brain switches gears.
喋れなくなるんです。今、歌の脳になってるんだ？
And I can't speak properly anymore. Oh, you're in singing mode now?
そう、今日はもう喋れません！じゃあ、このまま置いておこう。
Yes, so I can't speak today! Let's just leave you like that then.
なんでですか！本当に呼んでくれてありがとう！
Why?! But really, thank you so much for inviting me!
こちらこそ！一緒に歌えるのが本当に嬉しくて。次はしっとり行きます！
Same here! I'm so glad we can sing together. Next up is the quiet corner!
そして！ホロライブ6期生、holoXの頭脳、博衣こよりだよ！
And! From Hololive 6th Gen, HoloX's brain, Hakui Koyori!
第2回もこうして皆さんに来ていただいて開催できて嬉しいです！
I'm so happy we could hold this second concert with all of you here!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you!
そして、今日、ピアノは、前回に引き続きWingさんに弾いていただきますよ！
And today, playing the piano, we have Wing-san once again!
おおー！すごい！
Oh! Amazing!
一緒にみんなで礼するやつじゃない？
Isn't this the tune where everyone bows together?
キリツ、レイ、チャクセキ！
Stand up, bow, sit down!
なにこれ！学校みたい！これ、ジャパニーズ・スクール？
What is this?! Like school! Is this Japanese school style?
そうそう！そうなんですか？じゃあ、もう一回！
Yes! Really? Let's do it one more time!
キリツ、レイ、チャクセキ！
Stand up, bow, sit down!
ありがとうございます！体験できた！学校が始まった！
Thank you! You got to experience it! School has started!
そして、今回もですね、完全生3Dライブということで…
And once again, this is a fully live 3D performance...
最初から最後まで生でお届けしますので、優しい目で見守ってください！
So we will perform live from start to finish. Please watch over us warmly!
ハッシュタグはこちら、#holoAcousticLive となっております！
The hashtag is #holoAcousticLive!
そして、#博衣こより超重大告知 というのもありまして。
And we also have the hashtag #HakuiKoyoriSuperImportantAnnouncement.
本日は途中で告知もありますので、ぜひ最後まで見ていってください！
We will have an announcement in the middle, so please watch until the end!
では、ここからは、2人ずつ順番に歌っていく…
Now then, from here on, we will sing in duets...
しっとりコーナーに行こうかと思います。
For our quiet and emotional corner.
最初に一緒に歌ってくれるのは？誰だ？誰だ？
Who will be singing with me first? Who is it? Who is it?
はい！ガチャ？ガチャじゃない！
Yes! Is it a gacha? It's not a gacha!
ガチャで当たったのは、あずちゃん！
The one selected from the gacha is AZ-chan!
それでは、歌いたいと思います。他の皆さんはゆっくりしていってください。
Well then, we are going to sing. The rest of you, please go rest.
ありがとう！バイバイ！
Thank you! Bye-bye!
ということで、今日は、「イン・オータム」ということで、秋っぽい曲を…
So, with today's theme "In Autumn", we have autumn-like songs...
集めましたよ。これは、一緒に歌いたかった！
Gathered here. I really wanted to sing this song together!
そう、あずちゃんが言ってくれて、歌えることになって超ハッピー！
Yes, AZ-chan suggested it, and I'm super happy we can sing it!
超ハッピーです！選曲させていただきました。歌わせてもらいます。
I'm super happy too! We selected this song to perform for you.
では、タイトルコール、お願いしちゃいましょうかね。聞いてください。
Now then, could you introduce the song title? Please listen.
「暁の車」。
"Akatsuki no Kuruma."
風さそう…
The wind invites...
木陰にうつぶせになって泣いてた
I was crying, lying face down in the shade of the trees
見も知らぬ私を私が見ていた
I was watching my completely unfamiliar self
逝く人の調べを奏でるギタァーラ
A guitarra plays the melody of those who pass away
来ぬ人の嘆きに星は落ちて
Stars fall at the grief of those who will not return
行かないで どんなに叫んでも
No matter how much I scream, "Don't go!"
オレンジの花びら 静かに揺れるだけ
The orange petals only sway in silence
やわらかな手につむがれた
Spun by soft hands
遠い日に残された
left behind in the distant days
手のひらの希望を育む
fostering the hope in the palm of my hand
とこしえのさようなら つまびく
strumming an eternal farewell
優しい手にすがる子供の心を
The child's heart clinging to gentle hands
燃えさかる車は振り払い進む
The burning wheel shakes off and moves forward
逝く人の嘆きを奏でて ギタァーラ
A guitarra plays the grief of those who pass away
胸の火を激しくかき鳴らして
violently strumming the fire in my heart
あやまちに染まらない白さで
With a whiteness untainted by mistakes
オレンジの花びら 揺れてた 夏の影に
the orange petals were swaying in the shadow of summer
やわらかな日々を失くしても
Even if we lose those soft days
赤く染めた砂を遙か
far beyond the red-stained sand
超えてゆく さようなら
we will cross over... to the rhythm...
のリズム
...of farewell.
思い出を焼き尽くして進む大地に
On the earth where we move forward, burning up our memories,
懐かしく芽吹いていくものがあるの
there is something sprouting that fills us with nostalgia
暁の車を見送って
Watching the car of dawn depart
オレンジの花びら 揺れてる 今もどこか
the orange petals are swaying, even now, somewhere
いつか見た安らかな夜明けを
The peaceful dawn we once saw,
もう一度 手にするまで
until we hold it in our hands once more,
消さないで ともしび
don't extinguish the light,
車は
The wheel...
回るよ
...turns.
I am GOD'S CHILD
この腐敗した
left to fall into
世界に堕とされた
this corrupt world.
How do I live on such a field
こんなもののために
For something like this,
生まれたんじゃない
I wasn't born.
突風に舞う 足取り
My footsteps flutter in the sudden gust,
倒れそうになるのを
and as I am about to fall,
この鎖が許さない
these chains refuse to let me.
心は明け渡したままで
With my heart surrendered as is,
あなたの感覚だけが散らばって
only your sensations are scattered around,
私はまだ上手に片付けられずに
and I still cannot tidy them up well.
I am GOD'S CHILD
この腐敗した
left to fall into
世界に堕とされた
this corrupt world.
How do I live on such a field
こんなもののために
For something like this,
生まれたんじゃない
I wasn't born.
理由はもっと喋り続けて
Keep speaking of your reasons more,
私が眠れるまで
until I can fall asleep.
効かない薬ばかり転がってるけど
Only ineffective medicine rolls around,
ここに声もないのに一体何に信じれば?
but with no voice here, what on earth should I believe?
I am GOD'S CHILD
哀しい音は背中に爪跡を付けて
The sad sound leaves claw marks on my back.
I can't hang out this world
I can't hang out in this world,
こんな思いじゃ
with these kinds of feelings,
どこにも居場所なんてない
there is nowhere I belong.
不愉快に冷たい壁とか
Unpleasantly cold walls and such,
次はどれに弱さを許す?
which one will allow my weakness next?
終わりになって手を伸ばさないで あなたなら救い出して
Don't reach out your hand at the very end, if it's you, rescue me,
私を静寂から
from the silence.
時間は痛みを加速させて行く
Time continues to accelerate the pain.
I am GOD'S CHILD
この腐敗した
left to fall into
世界に堕とされた
this corrupt world.
How do I live on such a field
こんなもののために
For something like this,
生まれたんじゃない
I wasn't born.
I am GOD'S CHILD
哀しい音は背中に爪跡を付けて
The sad sound leaves claw marks on my back.
I can't hang out this world
I can't hang out in this world,
こんな思いじゃ
with these kinds of feelings,
どこにも居場所なんてない
there is nowhere I belong.
How do I live on such a field...
夕月夜 顔だす
The evening moon appears,
消えてく 子どもの声
as the children's voices fade away.
遠く 遠く
Far, far away,
この空のどこかに
somewhere in this sky,
君はいるんだろう
I know you must be there.
夏の終わりに 2人で抜け出した
At the end of summer, the two of us slipped away
この公園で見つけた
and found in this park
あの星座 何だか
that constellation. Do you somehow
覚えてる?
remember it?
会えなくても 記憶をたどって
Even if we can't meet, I'll trace my memories
同じ幸せを見たいんだ
because I want to see the same happiness.
あの香りと共に
Along with that scent,
花火が ぱっと開く
the fireworks suddenly burst open.
行きたいよ
I want to go
君のところへ
to where you are.
今すぐ かけだして 行きたいよ
I want to run to you right now.
まっ暗で何も 見えない
It's pitch black, and I can't see anything,
怖くても大丈夫
but even if I'm scared, I'll be fine.
数えきれない星空が
An uncountable starry sky
今もずっと ここにあるんだよ
is still right here, always.
泣かないよ
I won't cry,
昔 君と見た きれいな空だったから
for it's the beautiful sky we once looked at together.
あの道まで 響く
Echoing all the way to that road,
靴の音が耳に残る
the sound of footsteps lingers in my ears.
大きな 自分の影を
Staring at my own large shadow,
見つめて 想うのでしょう
I suppose I'll think of you.
ちっとも変わらないはずなのに
Even though nothing should have changed,
切ない気持ち ふくらんでく
this painful feeling keeps growing.
どんなに思いたって
No matter how much I yearn,
君はもういない
you're no longer here.
行きたいよ
I want to go
君のそばに
to your side.
小さくても 小さくても
Even if I'm small, so very small,
一番に 君が好きだよ
I love you more than anyone else.
強く いられる
I can be strong.
願いを流れ星に
I gently whispered my wish
そっととなえてみたけれど
to a falling star, but...
泣かないよ
I won't cry,
届くだろう
for surely it will reach
きれいな空に
into the beautiful sky.
会えなくても 記憶をたどって
Even if we can't meet, I'll trace my memories
同じ幸せを見たいんだ
because I want to see the same happiness.
あの香りと共に
Along with that scent,
花火が ぱっと開く
the fireworks suddenly burst open.
行きたいよ
I want to go
君のところへ
to where you are,
小さな手を 握りしめて
holding your small hand tight.
泣きたいよ
I want to cry,
それはそれは きれいな空だった
for it was such a beautiful, beautiful sky.
願いを流れ星に
I gently whispered my wish
そっととなえてみたけれど
to a falling star, but...
泣きたいよ
I want to cry,
届かない想いを この空に...
sending my unreachable feelings into this sky...
プラネタリウム
[Song: Planetarium]
ずっと一緒にいた
We were always together,
二人で歩いた一本道
walking down this single path as two.
二つに分かれて
Splitting into two,
別々の方歩いてく
we walk in separate directions.
寂しさで溢れたこの胸かかえて
Holding onto this chest overflowing with loneliness,
今にも泣き出しそうな空見上げて
looking up at a sky that seems ready to cry at any moment,
あなたを想った
I thought of you...
君がいない夜だって
Even on nights without you,
そう no more cry もう泣かないよ
that's right, no more cry, I won't cry anymore.
がんばっているからねって
I'll tell myself, "I'm doing my best,"
強くなるからねって
and "I will become stronger."
君も見ているだろう
You must be looking at it too,
この消えそうな三日月
this crescent moon that seems ready to fade away.
つながっているからねって
"Because we are connected," I tell myself,
愛してるからねって
and "Because I love you."
冷えきった手を
My hands grown cold...
一人で温める日々
These days of warming them all by myself.
君のぬくもり
Your warmth,
恋しくて 恋しくて
I miss it so, I miss it so much.
どれだけ電話で「好き」と言われたって
No matter how many times you tell me "I love you" over the phone,
君に寄りかかることはできない
I cannot lean on you.
涙をぬぐった...
Wiping away my tears...
君がいない夜だって
Even on nights without you,
そう no more cry もう泣かないよ
that's right, no more cry, I won't cry anymore.
がんばっているからねって
I'm doing my best, you see...
強くなるからねって
I'll become stronger, you see...
今度いつ会えるんだろう
When will we be able to meet next?
それまでの電池は
The energy to keep me going until then...
抱きしめながら言った
are the words you said while holding me tight:
あなたの「愛してる」の一言
Your simple "I love you."
君がいない夜だって
Even on nights without you,
そう no more cry もう泣かないよ
that's right, no more cry, I won't cry anymore.
がんばっているからねって
Saying, "I'm doing my best,"
強くなるからねって
and "I will become stronger."
君も見ているだろう
You must be looking at it too,
この消えそうな三日月
this crescent moon that seems ready to fade away.
つながっているからねって
"Because we are connected,"
愛してるからねって
and "Because I love you."
三日月 手をのばした
I reached my hand out to the crescent moon,
君に届けこの想い
may these feelings reach you.
はい！ということで、4曲続けて2人ずつお届けさせていただきました！みなさん！
Yes! And with that, we brought you four songs in a row, performed in pairs! Everyone!
あつまれ！
Gather round!
あつまれー！
めっちゃくちゃいいじゃないですか！
Wasn't that absolutely wonderful?!
最高じゃないですか！
Isn't it just the best?!
すごい！
Amazing!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
では ちょっと2曲目から振り返ってみよう
Now, let's look back starting from the second song...
...と思うんですけれども、
...is what I thought, but...
まずはAZKiの「青い車」！
first, AZKi's "Aoi Kuruma"!
いや、素晴かったですね！
Wow, that was wonderful!
いや、素晴らしかったですね。
Yes, it was wonderful.
この曲、くーちゃんと歌えたのめっちゃ嬉しいです！
I'm so happy I got to sing this song with Ku-chan!
こよも！
Me too!
嬉しい！なんかこの秋に...
I'm happy! Somehow, in this autumn...
誘われる...
Invited...
誘われた、誘われた！すいません、すいません。
I was invited, I was! Sorry, sorry.
はい、めちゃくちゃピアノも素敵で。
Yes, the piano was also wonderful.
いや本当にね、この曲...
Indeed, this song...
ギターアラって言うから、本当にギターがすごい鳴る曲なんですけど、
It's called "Guitar ala", so it's a song where the guitar really rings out,
ピアノオンリーになると、こういう感じなんだなって。
but when it's piano-only, it feels like this.
いや、よかったです。
Yeah, it was great.
しっとり歌わせていただきました。ありがとうございます。
We sang it in a mellow way. Thank you very much.
ありがとうございました。
Thank you very much.
めっちゃ真ん中きまずい！
Being in the middle is so awkward!
次、次、次！めちゃ真ん中きまずい、本当に。
Next, next, next! It's really awkward in the middle, seriously.
どうぞ、トワ様、トワ様どうぞ。
Go ahead, Towa-sama, Towa-sama, go ahead.
こよりね、トワ様の声でも再生されてたもん、合いすぎて。
Koyori could even hear it in Towa-sama's voice, it suited you so much.
本当に？
Really?
え、歌えてたかな？
Uh, did I sing it well?
え、超よかった！
Uh, it was super good!
意外と緊張しちゃったんだけど、やだちょっと。
I actually got surprisingly nervous, oh my.
え、めっちゃよかった！こよりが一生緊張してたんで、
No, it was amazing! Koyori was nervous the whole time,
すごい硬かった。
so I was really stiff.
うそ！
No way!
こんにちは！
Hello!
みこち！
Miko-chi!
来ましたね！
You made it!
こよちゃんの枠でね
Here on Koyo-chan's stream...
ええ
Yeah...
ちょっとドキドキの2人のデュエットをさせて
We're going to perform a slightly nerve-wracking duet
いただこうかなと思います！
together!
ぜひお願いします
Please do!
では、準備はよろしいですか？
So, are you ready?
はい
Yes.
はい！
Yes!
それではお聞きください。せーの
Now, please listen... ready, set...
スペシャルメドレー！
Special Medley!
息をしている
I'm breathing,
だから生きている
so I am alive.
何度もずっと言葉を贈ってきたんだ//
I've sent my words to you over and over again.
息をしている
I'm breathing,
世に見えている
visible to the world.
青が染み出す 私にとっての何か
The blue seeps out, becoming something to me.
鼓動がドクドクしている
My heart is throbbing.
ここはいつも変わらずに
This place always remains unchanged,
急かし続ける
constantly rushing...
ボタン一つの命
a life controlled by a single button.
最後まで私のこと覚えててくれるの？
Will you remember me until the very end?
消えてしまいそうなの わかってよ わかってよ ねぇ
I feel like I'm about to disappear, please understand, please understand, hey.
本当は本当はどうなの いずれは卒業するんでしょう
What is the truth, really? We'll graduate eventually, right?
日常に戻ったら 私は いなくなるの
When things go back to daily life, will I disappear?
いのちのような
As if experiencing...
夢を見てるよ
a dream like life itself.
またね バイバイ
See you later, bye bye.
自信なんてなかった 1人だってよかった
I had no confidence, I was fine being alone,
プライドに隠れて
hiding behind my pride.
誰かの視線気になってばかりで閉じこもってた
Always worrying about how others saw me, I shut myself away.
嫌いだなんて思えなくて
I couldn't bring myself to hate it,
笑えなかったんだ
and I couldn't laugh.
涙で滲んだ画面の向こう
Beyond the screen blurred with tears,
不意に溶けた心
my heart suddenly melted.
触れてくれた声
The voice that reached out to me,
君のおかげで笑えたよ
thanks to you, I was able to smile.
その言葉がずっと
Those words will always...
この胸を灯す
...light up this chest of mine
ただ一つの光
as my one and only light.
Fire, take me higher
消えそうな声を歌に変えて
turning a voice about to disappear into a song.
弱さ抱きしめながら
While embracing my weakness,
届けと叫ぶように燃やす
I burn it as if crying out to reach you...
炎を
...the flame.
The flame.
Fire, take me higher
君の明日を
I want to light up...
照らしたい
...your tomorrow.
黙ってうつむいて 空の色さえ
Looking down in silence, even the color of the sky...
知らない私の
...was unknown to me.
声で君が笑った
Since you laughed at my voice,
あの日から世界は眩しくて
the world has been so bright.
私は私を好きになって
I've come to like myself,
なくさないように息をする
and I breathe so I won't lose it.
暗闇のような青の
In the middle of the dark,
真ん中で今も泣いているのは
blue-like darkness, the reason I'm still crying...
君が写る世界が
is because the world reflecting you
悲しくなるほど優しいから
is kind enough to make me sad.
苦しくなるほど遠いから
Because it's far enough to make me suffer.
チクチクとウズウズ甘い熱を
The tingling and aching sweet heat,
閉じ込めていたのに 痛くて零れた
I kept it locked away, but it spilled out from the pain.
きっと私と体の 体の間にある
Surely, even the extremely thin skin
ひどく薄い皮膚さえ もう邪魔になるくらい
between my body and yours is almost getting in the way now.
その鼓膜 その心臓
If I could touch that eardrum,
ずっと奥に触れたら 君はまた笑うのかな
and that heart deep inside, would you laugh again?
届いて 君まで届け
Please, let it reach you.
I recognize the face staring back at me today
I guess it's time to change
La la la la la
When I don't feel like myself
I don't need someone else
Guess I'll just change my dress
And energy will stay stateless
You can't cage me up, I'm the key
I can't move on in a heartbeat
They can feel, feel, feel my vibe
Feel, feel, feel my vibe, like me
In the night, I'm just moving to the rhythm of a different life
They can feel, feel, feel my vibe
Feel, feel, feel my vibe, like me
Step back, cuz tomorrow I'm the girl you met tonight
Switch it up, ooh-ooh-ooh
I just want to feel my heart, just feel my heart
Go boom boom boom
Switch it up, ooh-ooh-ooh
Every time I've had enough of who I was
I swear that I'll just switch it up again
いいないいな このまま 溢れ出しちゃうくらいに
It's great, it's great, just like this, so much that it overflows!
あともちょっと そのまま これを3滴か 4滴か ちょちょちょいと
Just a little longer like that, is this 3 drops or 4 drops? Just a tiny bit...
ちょいと私で退けないってどういうこと？
Wait, what do you mean you won't back down for me?
そんなショイでウブめな君も行っちゃって 行っちゃって！
Even you, who are so shy and naive, just go for it, go for it!
ピンクになってこ 全人類
Let's turn pink, all of humanity!
両手にピースで はいホッピー
Peace signs in both hands, yes, hoppy!
飛んでけ羞恥心
Fly away, embarrassment!
持ってけ白衣
Take it away, lab coat!
ピンクになってよ 全人類
Turn pink, all of humanity!
誰も彼も全部
Everyone and everything, all of it!
いいでしょ いいよね 絶対楽しいよ
It's fine, right? It's good, right? It's definitely going to be fun!
ピンクになってこ 全人類
Let's turn pink, all of humanity!
ピンクになってよ 全人類
Turn pink, all of humanity!
ピンク色の頭が 世界を救う！
Our pink heads will save the world!
できたー！
We did it!
オリジナル曲スペシャルシャッフルメドレーでしたー！
That was the Original Song Special Shuffle Medley!
今歌った最後の曲はですね
The last song we just sang
本日リリースした HoneyWorksさんによる「ピンクになっちゃえ」という曲なんですけど
is "Pink ni Nacchae" by HoneyWorks, which was released today!
このステージ、そしてみんなの手元もちょっとピンクに染め上げさせていただいたところです！
We've dyed this stage and everyone's glowsticks pink!
ピンクになっちゃった！
We turned pink!
なっちゃった、なっちゃった！
Turned pink, turned pink!
みんなピンク！ イェーイ！
Everyone is pink! Yay!
はい、ということで！ ここでこよりからの
All right, with that! Right here, from Koyori...
超超超重大なお知らせをさせていただこうと思います！
I have a super-duper major announcement to share with you all!
ですがね、告知の後に全員でもう一曲歌いますので
But, after the announcement, we will sing one more song together, so...
え、そうだったんだ！
Oh, really?!
私、まだ知らない...
I didn't know that yet...
全然何にも知らないやん！
We didn't know anything about it!
何にも知らないトワ様
Towa-sama knows absolutely nothing!
ということで、皆さん最後までチャンネルはそのままで見ていってくださいね！
So everyone, please keep your channels tuned right here until the very end!
それでは！
And now!
ご覧ください！
Please have a look!
特報
[Breaking News]
えーまずオリジナル曲を作りたい
First, I want to make an original song.
なんと博衣こより初めてのオリジナル曲...
Wow, Hakui Koyori's very first original song...
ファーストアルバムどうだったかな？
How was the first album?
こよりにはいっぱい いっぱい、夢がある
Koyori has so, so many dreams,
全ての夢を叶えるのが夢
and making all of them come true is her dream.
叶えていけるように
So that she can make them all come true...
夢のソロライブに みんなを連れて行きたい
I want to take everyone to my dream solo concert.
博衣こより 1st Live 開催決定
[Hakui Koyori 1st Live Announced!]
2026.12.22
[December 22, 2026]
TOKYO GARDEN THEATER
Hakui Koyori 1st Live Dream Spark
はい！ということで、2026年12月22日
Alright! So, on December 22, 2026,
東京ガーデンシアターにて、博衣こより1st Live「Dream Spark」の開催が決定いたしました！
at Tokyo Garden Theater, Hakui Koyori's 1st Live
"Dream Spark" has been officially announced!
イェーイ！おめでとう！
Yay! Congratulations!
はい、ついに夢の一つであるソロライブが決まりました！ありがとうございます！
Yes! Finally, one of my dreams, a solo concert,
has been decided! Thank you so much!
はい、今年できるとは思っていなかったので
I didn't think I'd be able to do it this year,
みんなも、もっと早くてびっくりしてると思うんですけど
so I'm sure everyone is surprised
that it's so soon.
精一杯、頑張っていくので応援よろしくお願いします！
I will do my absolute best,
so please support me!
そして、今回のライブのハッシュタグは「#夢煌めけこより」となっております！
Also, the hashtag for this concert
is "#夢煌めけこより"!
ぜひこちらで呟いてください！
Please use this hashtag to tweet about it!
ちなみに、これセカンドアルバムのハッシュタグも同じ「#夢煌めけこより」でやっていくので
By the way, we'll use the same hashtag,
"#夢煌めけこより", for the 2nd album as well,
どんどんポストしていただけると嬉しいです！
so I'd be very happy
if you kept posting with it!
ライブの詳しい情報については、後日発表予定となります。
Detailed information about the concert
will be announced at a later date.
皆さん、まずは12月22日、にゃんにゃんの日
Everyone, first of all, December 22,
the "Nyan Nyan" day,
ぜひ予定を空けて待っててください！
please make sure to keep your schedules open
and wait for it!
そして、さらに！こよりのセカンドアルバム
And what's more! Koyori's 2nd album,
「Chemical Spark」が12月2日に発売決定となりました！
"Chemical Spark," is set to be released
on December 2!
ドン！
Ba-bam!
はい、今回はホロライブオフィシャルショップ限定販売の完全生産限定盤と
Yes, this time we have the Limited Edition,
sold exclusively on the Hololive Official Shop,
こより初の全国流通での販売もある通常盤の2種類となります！
and the Regular Edition, which will be Koyori's
first nationwide distribution release!
アルバムには書き下ろしの新曲のほか
In addition to newly written songs for this album,
CD限定の曲などもありますので、是非ともお聞きください！
it also includes CD-exclusive tracks,
so please give it a listen!
えー、まずは完全生産限定盤の同梱物についてご紹介します。こちらです！
First, let me introduce the contents included
in the Limited Edition. Here they are!
はい、えー、アルバムのイラストを使ったアクスタやホロカのほか
Along with an acrylic stand using the album
illustration and a hololive card,
こよりからの思いを込めたお手紙
a letter filled with Koyori's feelings,
そして、直筆で皆さんにサインを書いたアナザージャケットがついてきます！
and also an alternative jacket
featuring my hand-written signature!
買ってくれた助手くんみんなのために頑張るので、えー、ぜひ手に入れてください！
I'll do my best for all the Assistants who buy it,
so please get your hands on it!
とっても豪華な、六角形！このね、こよりの頭についているベンゼン環と
It comes in a very luxurious hexagon!
It's the same shape as the benzene ring on Koyori's head,
同じ形のスペシャルBOXパッケージとなっております！お楽しみに！
a special box package in the same shape!
Look forward to it!
さらに、なんと！完全生産限定盤の予約特典として
Furthermore, as a pre-order bonus
for the Limited Edition,
先ほど発表したソロライブの先行抽選シリアルコードがついてまいります！
you will get an early lottery application serial code
for the solo live concert we just announced!
シリアルコードが付属するのは、完全生産限定盤のみ！
The serial code is only included
in the Limited Edition!
そして、あの、期間もあるので、えー、お気をつけください。
And there is a specific period for it,
so please be careful.
シリアルコードは、ご注文1件につき1つつきますが
You will receive one serial code per order,
複数購入しても、応募で使えるコードは1つだけなのでご注意ください。
but please note that even if you purchase multiple copies,
only one code can be used per application.
えー、そしてシリアルコードはですね、ライブチケット抽選への応募権となりまして
Also, the serial code serves as the right
to apply for the ticket lottery,
当選を保証するものではないこと
so it does not guarantee winning a ticket.
そして、当選時にチケット購入の代金も追加で必要になりますので、そちらはご了承下さい。
Also, if you win, the ticket purchase fee will be
required separately, so please keep that in mind.
その他詳しくは、ホロライブオフィシャルショップの販売ページを必ずチェックしてくださいね！
For other details, please make sure to check
the product page on the Hololive Official Shop!
はい、そしてこちらが通常盤の同梱物です！
And here are the contents included
in the Regular Edition!
はい、初回プレス限定で、全5種類のランダムアナザージャケットが1枚入っています！
Yes! The first press limited edition includes one random
alternative jacket out of five designs!
これは、ファーストアルバムと同じ形にさせていただきました！
This is the same format as my first album!
それぞれ、違った... 大丈夫か？
Each features a different... Are you guys okay?
それぞれ違ったイラストレーターさんにイラストを書き下ろしていただいておりますよ！
Each features a different illustration
drawn specially by various illustrators!
え、ちょっと動物園になってますけど、後ろが。はい。
The background is turning a bit into a zoo. Yes.
さらにですね、そこに数量限定ランダムで...
And what's more, as a limited-quantity random bonus...
こよりの直筆サインが入っているかもしれません！
...my handwritten signature might be in it!
当たったらラッキー！ということで、おみくじ感覚でご購入ください！
If you get it, you're lucky! Think of it like drawing a fortune when you buy it!
そして！店舗さんでの特典アイテムはこちらになっております！ドン！
And! The bonus items from store purchases are right here! Ta-da!
はい、それぞれ素敵なアイテムをご用意いたしました！
Yes, we have prepared wonderful items at each store!
そしてなんとですね、秋葉原ゲーマーズ本店さんでリリースイベントを2027年1月8日に開催いたします！
And guess what! We will be holding a release event at Akihabara Gamers Main Store on January 8th, 2027!
ゲーマーズさんでCDをご予約、購入すると抽選に応募できますので、詳細はゲーマーズさんのウェブサイトをチェックしてみて下さい！
If you pre-order or purchase the CD from Gamers, you can enter the raffle! Please check Gamers' website for details!
ちなみに、先ほど披露したアルバムにも収録される、ジョンやきとりさん作の、新曲「ピンクになっちゃう！」のMVを、
By the way, the MV for the new song "Become Pink!" written by john-yakitori, which is also on the album...
このライブ終了後にプレミア公開させていただきますので、ぜひ見に行ってください！
...will be premiered right after this live stream ends, so please go watch it!
ジョンやきとりさんといつも一緒にやっている、103さんに、103bushのMV作っていただいてますので、見てください！
The MV was created by 103, who often collaborates with john-yakitori, and 103bush, so please check it out!
以上、アルバムはこの後21時より予約開始です！ご注目ください！
That's all! Pre-orders for the album will start today at 21:00! Please look forward to it!
さらに実は、もう一つ重大告知がありまして、ドドン！
Furthermore, we actually have one more major announcement! Ta-da!
ドン！はい、TOKYO FMさんにて10月に1ヶ月限定の特別番組の放送が決定いたしました！イェーイ！
Ta-da! Yes! A special one-month limited program on TOKYO FM has been confirmed for October! Yay!
大好きなラジオ、そして冠番組が、よく聞いていたTOKYO FMさんでできるのがすごく嬉しいです！ありがとうございます！
I'm so happy to have my own show on TOKYO FM, a radio station I've listened to so much! Thank you!
オンエア日時などは後日発表させていただきますので、お楽しみに！
The broadcast dates and times will be announced later, so please look forward to it!
告知は以上となります！皆さん大変お待たせいたしました！
That's all for the announcements! Everyone, sorry to keep you waiting!
「お待たせしました！」 「待ってていただいてありがとうございます！」
"Sorry to keep you waiting!" "Thank you for waiting for us!"
ということで、お届けしました、ホロアコースティックライブ第2回だったんですけれども、
And with that, we presented the 2nd Holo Acoustic Live, but...
この後もう1曲歌うので、皆さん待っててくださいね。みんなで歌いますからね！
...we still have one more song after this, so please wait for it. We'll all sing together!
はい、じゃあ、ちょっと皆さんに1人ずつ感想とか、あと、もしなんか告知とかあったらしてってください。では、にこちゃん！
Yes, let's hear everyone's thoughts one by one, and if you have any announcements, please share them. First, Niko-chan!
いや、あの、こんな一番の後輩が言わせてもらうのはあれなんですけど、言わせてもらう、言うのも変なんですけど、
Well, as the most junior member, it might be a bit awkward for me to say, or weird to bring up...
こよ先輩の、本当に頑張り屋さんなところがいろんなところから感じられて、
...but I could really feel how hard-working Koyo-senpai is from so many different things.
なんか、最初トワ様が歌詞のこと言ってたやん？「いや、笑っちゃうわ」とか思ってたら、なんかそこにも感動してきちゃって。
At first, when Towa-sama was talking about the lyrics, I was like, "Wow, that's funny," but then I started getting touched by that too.
なんか一生懸命やっててね、愛を感じる。
Seeing you work so hard, I really felt the love.
愛を感じる。本当に、笑うかも。ごめん、やっぱり笑うかもしれない。笑っていいんだよ！
I felt the love. Seriously, I might laugh. Sorry, I actually might laugh. It's fine to laugh!
でも本当にこんな素敵なライブに参加させてもらえたこと、そして重大発表も本当におめでとうございます！
But really, thank you so much for letting me participate in such a wonderful live stream, and congrats on the major announcements!
またぜひ参加させてください！ありがとうございます！
Please let me join again sometime! Thank you!
じゃあコボ先輩！はい！まず、
Next, Kobo-senpai! Yes! First,
セカンドアルバムおめでとう！センキュー！テリマカシ！えー、ファーストソロライブおめでとう！テリマカシ！
Congratulations on your second album! Thank you! Terima kasih! And congrats on your first solo live! Terima kasih!
で、私は歌うのが好き。だからここは嬉しい。嬉しい！
And, I love singing. So I'm really happy to be here. I'm so glad!
ゲストに、ゲストに呼んでくれてありがとう！
Thank you so much for inviting me as a guest!
来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for coming!
コボ上手！欲しいもの何でも言うのよ。欲しいもの何でも言うのよ。プレゼント。高いもの。高いものでもいいのよ。
Kobo is so good! Tell me whatever you want. I'll get you anything you want as a present. Even something expensive.
高いものオッケー？オッケー！マンション！マンション？！マンションは無理、マンションは無理！
Something expensive is okay? Okay! A mansion! A mansion?! No, a mansion is impossible!
やめろ、ニコ。後でね、後でね。何でもいいのよ。
Stop it, Niko. Later, later. Anything is fine.
ありがとう、本当に。嬉しい！また歌おう！はい、いつでも、いつでも。
Thank you, truly. I'm so happy! Let's sing together again! Yes, anytime, anytime.
いつでも、本当に？呼んじゃうよ？イエス！ありがとう！イエス！
Anytime, really? I'll invite you again, okay? Yes! Thank you! Yes!
とても可愛い。ありがとう。そしてトワ様！はい！
So cute. Thank you. And next, Towa-sama! Yes!
あのね、みんなと歌えたのがすごい嬉しかったです。まずは。
You know, first of all, I was really happy that we could sing together.
あとね、やっぱりあのニコも言ってたけど、こよりがね、いろんな企画とかで絡むことっていうか、
And also, as Niko mentioned, Koyori and I interact in various projects, and...
一緒にやることがあるんですけど、ひとつひとつのものに本当に全力投球というか、
...we get to do things together, and she always gives 100% to every single thing.
一生懸命頑張るのを裏でも見てきたので、本当にソロライブできておめでとうという気持ちです！
I've seen her working so hard behind the scenes too, so I'm genuinely happy she gets to hold a solo live! Congrats!
ありがとうございます。頑張ります、もっと頑張ります！緊張しました今日も。
Thank you so much. I'll do my best, I'll work even harder! I was so nervous today too.
そうだね、ソロライブまで大変かもしれないけど、全力でまた頑張ってくださいね。
Yeah, it might be tough preparing for the solo live, but please keep giving it your all!
ありがとう、先輩！はい、先輩です！先輩風吹かせとくぜ！ありがとうございます！
Thank you, Senpai! Yes, I'm your senpai! Let me act like a proud senpai! Thank you so much!
はい、そしてアズキ！はい！えー、まずはソロライブ開催と、アルバム発売おめでとうございます！
Yes, and next, AZKi! Yes! First of all, congratulations on your solo live and album release!
本当に、もうこよちゃんは人の何倍も何倍も頑張っている、本当に...
Truly, Koyo-chan is working many times harder than normal people...
努力を
effort...
多分、いっぱいしてきて、今日があって
She probably put in a lot of it to reach today.
なんかあの、もう、ティザーで泣きそうになりました
Honestly, even the teaser almost made me cry.
本当だね / わかるわかる
That's so true. / I get it, I get it.
泣きそうになった、もう
I really almost cried.
これが全部今に繋がって
All of that connected to the present,
今日があるし、これからまた、もっと忙しくなると思いますけど
leading to today, and while you'll probably get even busier from now on,
みんなにいっぱい夢を与えてくださいね
please continue to give everyone lots of dreams!
します！
I will!
今日はありがとうございました
Thank you so much for today.
こちらこそ！
Likewise!
またぜひ、第3回も
And let's definitely do a third time.
さ、さすがにちょっとおこがましいかなと思いながら、
Though, I thought that might be a bit too presumptuous of me...
あの、一緒にやってるみたいな気持ちになって、勝手に
I just personally felt like we were doing it together!
ありがとうございます、いつもお世話になってます。ありがとうございます。
Thank you so much, thank you for always taking care of me.
はい、ということでね、今日はちょっと緊張しすぎたし、
Yes, so today I was way too nervous,
あの、はっちゃけすぎて息切れしましたし、ちょっと恥ずかしかったんですけど、
and got out of breath from fooling around, which was a bit embarrassing,
トータル自分は、
but in the end...
自分は本当に恥ずかしかったんですけども、
I was indeed really embarrassed, but
みんなと一緒に歌えたこの場がとっても楽しくて、幸せでございました！
being able to sing here with everyone was so much fun and made me so happy!
本当にありがとうございました！
Thank you all so much!
こちらこそ！
Likewise!
はい、この後も精進いたしますので、ぜひお見守りください。よろしくお願いします！
I will continue to work hard, so please keep supporting me! Thank you!
はい！ / はい！
Yes! / Yes!
それでは！
And now!
え、なんかお知らせとか大丈夫ですか？
Wait, is there any announcement you need to make?
いいですよ、いいですよ
It's fine, it's fine.
あなたが主役だから
Since you're the star of the show.
チャンネル登録をしてください、よろしくお願いします！
Please subscribe to my channel! Thank you!
概要欄にありますので、よろしくお願いします！
The link is in the description, so please subscribe!
それじゃあ、最後にちょっと一緒に歌わせていただきます。
Well then, to finish, we'd like to sing together.
はい！
Yes!
では、最後には、
Now, for our final song,
お聞きください！
please listen to...
Our Bright Parade!
[曲名: Our Bright Parade]
[Song: Our Bright Parade]
パレード パレード パレード 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, let's shine!
呼び合う声を合図に
With the sound of our calling voices as our cue.
パレード パレード パレード 探しにゆく
Parade, parade, parade, we go searching.
スタートは何度だって
No matter how many times we start over.
イェーイ！
Yay!
ほら、本当にソロライブとセカンドアルバムおめでとう！
Look, congratulations on your solo live and second album!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
みんな本当にありがとう！
Thank you so much, everyone!
ただ 一つずつ紡いだ
We just spun them one by one...
ただ 始まりたくて走った
We just ran because we wanted to start...
遠く 暗がりに灯った
Far away, lit in the darkness,
それは 眩しすぎた名前
was that dazzling name...
それは 優しすぎる思い出
was that incredibly gentle memory.
もっと 近づけと手を伸ばした
Reaching out to get even closer...
思いがけず結びあった
Unexpectedly, they tied together...
ほら
Look,
今
now,
迷い子は
the lost child
僕らに
has become
なった
"us."
パレード パレード パレード 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, let's shine!
悔しさも愛しさも連れておいで
Bring along both your regrets and your affection!
風 夢 晴れ 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, clear skies—we can take flight!
ささやかな祈りは光
Our modest prayers are light,
おわりなき予感
an endless premonition.
希望を見つけたこと
Finding hope...
胸を張れるよ
is something we can be proud of!
ここから
From here,
これから
from now on,
Our Bright Parade, Parade!
まだ 頼りない予感を
With a premonition still unreliable,
歌おう 恥ずかしくなんてないよ
let's sing! There's nothing to be ashamed of.
誰も 避けない今しがたり
The story of today that no one can avoid...
いつか また会えるおまじない
is a charm that we'll meet again someday.
あの日 ゼロの日に始まった
On that day, starting on day zero...
ストーリー
was our story.
数えきれない言葉は
Countless words...
数えるような想いじゃないさ
are not feelings that can be counted.
ほら今 僕らをひとつと呼ぼう
Look, now, let's call ourselves one!
パレード パレード パレード 美しいんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, it's beautiful!
許しあえる刹那な夜はきらめく
The transient nights where we can forgive each other sparkle.
雨 晴れ 風 また遠い空
Rain, clear skies, wind, and once again the distant sky...
ふさわしい旅路と
with a fitting journey...
...のは 君と歩くことさ
...is to walk with you.
君と歩くことなんだ
To walk with you.
「ただいま」を聞けば
If I hear "I'm home,"
「おかえり」って叫ぶよ
I'll shout "Welcome back!"
当たり前じゃないか
Of course, right?
パレ、パレ、パレード
Parade, parade, parade!
輝くんだよ
It's shining.
暗がりを満たすのは君だ、僕だ
The one who fills the darkness is you, is me.
パレ、パレ、パレード
Parade, parade, parade!
輝くんだよ
It's shining.
悔しさも愛おしさも連れておいで
Bring along both the frustration and the endearment.
風、夢、羽、飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, wings, we can take flight!
ささやかな祈りは光
Our modest prayers are the light,
終わりなき兆し
An endless sign,
君と飛び込んで行く 素敵なスタートさ
Plunging in with you, what a wonderful start.
心から これから Our Bright Parade, Parade!
From the bottom of my heart, from now on, Our Bright Parade, Parade!
Our Bright Parade, Parade!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
超超超！重大告知アリ！
完全生3D Acoustic Live in Autumn
[Super, Super, Super! Major Announcement!]
[Fully Live 3D Acoustic Live in Autumn]